whitecastle.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Notice | White Castle

Privacy Notice  
Posted 1/9/14  
Privacy Notice Table of Contents:  
1\. Our Commitment to Privacy   
2\. Types of Information We Collect and How It Is Used   
3\. Other Information Collected   
4\. Children   
5\. Our Commitment to Data Security   
6\. Changes to Our Privacy Notice   
7\. How to Contact Us   
8\. Sole Statement

## 1\. OUR COMMITMENT TO PRIVACY

White Castle White Castle Management Co. (“White Castle”) has developed this Privacy Notice (“Notice”) to describe the types of personal information we collect from visitors to this White Castle website (the “Site”) and to explain our online information practices as they relate to information submitted through the Site and specific communications as addressed herein which may or may not originate from this Site. This Notice is effective from the time it is posted on the Site, as noted above. To make this Notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and on every page through which personally identifiable information may be submitted. With respect to personally identifying information, White Castle collects and retains only information that you voluntarily submit to us.

USE OF OUR SITE CONSTITUTES AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS NOTICE. DO NOT USE THE SITE IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH ALL OF THE TERMS OF USE INCLUDING THIS NOTICE, THE SITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, AND ANY SUPPLEMENTAL NOTICE OR TERMS. WE MAKE WHAT WE BELIEVE TO BE COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE EFFORTS TO PROVIDE A REASONABLE LEVEL OF SECURITY FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION WE ARE REQUIRED TO PROTECT, BUT WE DO NOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION OR OTHER INFORMATION IN ANY FORM.

## 2\. TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW IT IS USED

Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information.  
Non-personal information can include certain personally identifiable information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. We obtain non-personal information about you from information that you provide us, either separately or together with your personally identifiable information. We also automatically collect certain non-personal information from you when you access our Site. This information can include, among other things, IP addresses, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, etc.), the third party website from which your visit originated, the operating system you are using (e.g., Vista, Windows XP, Mac OS, etc.), the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, NetZero, etc.), the search terms you use on our Site, the specific web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits.   
We use non-personal information in a variety of ways, including to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, carry out targeted promotional activities, and to improve our services. We may use your non-personal information by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others. We may share your non-personally identifying, anonymous information with our affiliated companies and third parties to achieve these objectives and others.   
IP Addresses.  
An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Internet. Web servers (computers that “serve up” web pages) automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When visitors request pages from our Site, our servers typically log their IP addresses. We collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report non-personal aggregate information to others, and to track the use of our Site. IP addresses are considered non-personal information and may also be shared as provided above. It is not our practice to link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable; that is, the visitor’s session will be logged, but the visitor remains anonymous to us.   
Cookies, etc.  
White Castle uses Cookies in the operation of the Site. “Cookies” are small text files from a website that are stored on your hard drive. These text files make using our Site more convenient by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. Cookies themselves do not typically contain any personally identifiable information. We may analyze the information derived from these cookies and other technological tools we employ (such as clear gifs/web beacons) and match this information with data provided by you or another party. We may provide our analysis and certain non-personal information to third parties (who may in turn use this information to provide tailored advertisements on the Site), but this will not involve disclosing any of your personally identifiable information. Please note that advertisers that serve advertisements on our Site and third-party content providers that serve content on our Site may also use their own cookies and other technological tools which are subject to the advertiser’s privacy policies, not this Privacy Notice.  
If you are concerned about the storage and use of cookies, you may be able to direct your internet browser to notify you and seek approval whenever a cookie is being sent to your hard drive. You may also delete a cookie manually from your hard drive through your internet browser or other programs. Please note, however, that some parts of our Site will not function properly or be available to you if you refuse to accept a cookie or choose to disable the acceptance of cookies.  
Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information.  
The Site collects only that personally identifiable information which is submitted voluntarily by you, and White Castle uses such information only for the purposes for which it was submitted, as further explained herein.   
Updates.  
By submitting your name, email address, and zip code through the “Get Updates” link or in any other place on the Site offering to send you updates or offers, you may subscribe to receive periodic updates about promotions, new menu items, merchandise, events, and other information relevant to White Castle delivered to your email inbox. You may opt out of receiving email messages and notifications by following the opt out instructions included with all messages delivered to your inbox. This information will be used solely for the purposes for which it was submitted and will not be shared with third parties (with the exception of third party services providers for purposes of their assisting us with providing the services which have been requested by you) or to track your online activities in a personally identifiable manner.   
Mobile Alerts/Promotional Text Messages.  
White Castle will not contact you by text message without your prior express written consent. White Castle will not sell or share your mobile phone number with unaffiliated parties other than with third party messaging services providers with whom White Castle has contracted. By submitting your mobile phone number and expressing your consent to a text messaging marketing campaign, alert service, or the like, you agree to the terms of that promotion, which likely include that White Castle may send to you by text message updates or offers, information about promotions, new menu items, merchandise, events, and other relevant information. You may opt out of receiving text messages or notifications by following the opt out instructions included with all such messages or by calling, toll free, 1-800-THE-CRAVE.  
ONLY INDIVIDUALS THIRTEEN (13) YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER MAY REQUEST EMAIL UPDATES OR MOBILE ALERTS/PROMOTIONAL TEXT MESSAGES.  
Sweepstakes/Contests.  
We may, at various times, use the Site to collect information for contests, promotions, or sweepstakes. When you enter information for any such contests, promotions, or sweepstakes, you will be subject to the official rules of that particular promotion. You may also receive informative email messages as a result of your entrance unless you have chosen to opt out of receiving such messages either at that time of sign up or in accordance with the opt out instructions included with the informative message(s) delivered to your email inbox. Winners may be required to return a completed prize acceptance form contained in the notification email by facsimile or U.S. mail and/or to execute (without limitation) tax acknowledgement forms, affidavits of eligibility, liability releases, and publicity releases (except where prohibited by law) within a designated time period. Please see the Official Rules located on the respective submission page of the Site for complete details.   
Contact Us Information.  
If you choose to contact us, we may collect information potentially including your name, email address, mailing address, phone number and your suggestion, question, comment, or customer service request. We use the information to process your suggestion or customer service request. We also will use this information to improve our products and services. For more information, please see the Terms and Conditions for Site Use.   
Disclosure Required.  
White Castle reserves the right to disclose any information you have submitted, without notice, if required to do so by law or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to:   
a) conform to the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served on White Castle or the Site;  
b) protect and defend the rights or property of White Castle; or,  
c) protect the personal safety of White Castle employees, associates, consumers, or the public.

## 3\. OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTED

Third Party Service Providers.  
We may use third party service providers for things such as the sale of gift cards or White Castle-branded apparel and gifts, or the provision of marketing services on behalf of White Castle. If you would like to purchase White Castle products through an online store, you may do so by navigating through the appropriate link on our Site. Apparel, gift cards, and other services may be provided by a third party, and you may have to leave our Site in order to visit the store or to make a purchase. Please note the domain address after clicking a link on our Site, and please review any terms and conditions and privacy policy or notice postings which appear through the links on the individual web pages. We do not have responsibility for or access to the information collected through an online store or other online function provided by a third party and are therefore not responsible for the security of that information and not liable for any breach of that security.   
Third Party Material or Links.  
We may from time to time contract with advertisers or other third parties who place information, advertisements, or other promotional material or links on our Site. If you click on an advertisement or other link provided by a third party and leave our Site, whether through a link or through visiting another website framed within our Site, you are subject to the privacy policies of these advertisers or other third parties. We do not have responsibility for, or access to, the information collected by these third parties. Any links from the Site to the website of a third party are not necessarily endorsements, sponsorships, or recommendations of the ideas, products, or services of the third party. White Castle is not liable for any damages, including indirect, incidental, special, or consequential, resulting from the use of, or information submitted through, third party websites.   
Employment Information.  
If you would like to become a White Castle employee, you may choose to search for job openings, sign up for job opening notification, or submit an employment application online through the “Employment” link. All information entered by you through the Employment function of the Site is collected by a third party service provider responsible for collecting the information and matching the information with White Castle job openings. The information collected through the application will be used by the service provider to match your credentials with White Castle job openings, of which you will be informed via your email address. If you choose to have your information remain anonymous, your personal information submitted through the Employment pages will not be shared with White Castle without your permission. White Castle is not responsible for the security of the information while retained exclusively by the third party service provider and is not liable for any breach of that security.   
You may apply for employment with White Castle by performing a job search, clicking on the job title, and clicking the “Apply Online” link. All information entered through the online application will be sent directly to White Castle and will be used only for purposes of review for employment and will not be shared with third parties or used for purposes other than as consistent with the terms of this Privacy Notice.   
Transfer of Assets.   
As we continue to develop our business, we may sell or purchase assets. If another entity acquires us or all (or substantially all) of our assets, the personally identifiable information and non-personal information we have about you will be transferred to and used by this acquiring entity, though we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your preferences are followed. Also, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, all such information may be considered an asset of ours and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.  
Public Forums/User Generated Content.   
We may offer chat rooms, blogs, message boards, bulletin boards, or similar public forums where you and other users of our Site can communicate or post photographic or other content. The protections described in this Privacy Notice do not apply when you provide information (including personal information) in connection with your use of these public forums. Please note that if a third party service provider is used in the process of loading photos or other content, you are subject to the privacy policies and terms of use of that third party service provider. We may use personally identifiable and non-personal information about you to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by anyone, including third parties that do not adhere to our Privacy Notice. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our Site.   
Information of Others.   
If you choose to submit the information of someone other than yourself without White Castle’s knowledge, the information will be handled in accordance with this Notice. You, however, are solely responsible and liable for any claims relating to your submission and use of that information.

## 4\. CHILDREN

The features, programs, promotions and other aspects of our Site requiring the submission of personally identifiable information are not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Do not provide any personal information unless you are at least 13 years of age. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us please contact us as provided in this Notice. A parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 may review and request deletion of such child’s personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use thereof.

## 5\. OUR COMMITMENT TO DATA SECURITY

The security of your personal information is important to us. None of the personal data collected is stored directly in the pages. We have further measures in place to protect your personal information once it reaches us.

## 6\. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY NOTICE

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Notice from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will notify you by displaying a new “Posted” date at the top of our Privacy Notice. USE OF THE SITE AFTER A CHANGE IN THE POSTED DATE WILL CONSTITUTE YOUR CONSENT TO THE AMENDMENTS TO THIS NOTICE. IF YOU DO NOT WANT TO BE BOUND BY AN AMENDED VERSION OF THIS NOTICE, DO NOT USE THE SITE AND CEASE AND DESIST ALL USE OF THE CONTENT OR SERVICES.

## 7\. HOW TO CONTACT US

For other information or questions regarding changing information that we have about you, please contact us at (614) 228-5781, or click on the “Contact Us” link located on our Site. You may also reach us at:

White Castle Management Co.  
555 W Goodale St.  
Columbus, OH 43215

## 8\. SOLE STATEMENT

This Privacy Notice as posted on this Site is the sole statement of our privacy practices with respect to this Site, and no summary, modification, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or notice, in any form, is valid unless we post a new or revised notice to the Site. Other privacy notices, policies, or terms may apply to particular activities related to White Castle but otherwise unrelated to the Site. For our Mobile Application Privacy Notice, please click here or go to <http://mobile.whitecastle.com/privacy-policy>.

Copyright © 2014, White Castle Management Co.  
All rights reserved.

* * *
